<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Informations>
  <Information name="DataAttribute">
    <description>
      With this interface you are able to manage (e.g. create, edit, delete) data attributes which may be used as variables in data structures (a variable is an instance of an attribute). Data attributes cannot be edited or deleted once they are associated with a data structure (they become locked).
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/RPM/Help/Index/#_Toc434570751"/>
  </Information>

  <Information name="Help">
    <description>
      This guide will walk you through the basics of using data planning including how to manage data types, units, data attributes and also structured and unstructured data structures.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path=""/>
  </Information>

  <Information name="DataStructureDesigner">
    <description>
      The Data Structure Manager is a tool to create, modify and delete Data Structures. Data Structures contain Variables, which are specific instances of Data Attributes.
      It is possible to create Data Structures for structured data (Excel tables, CSV-Files ...) and for unstructured data (images, videos ...).
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/RPM/Help/Index/#_Toc434570753"/>
  </Information>
  <Information name="DatatypeManager">
    <description>
      With this interface you are able to manage (e.g. create, edit, delete) data types which are required to define units and data attributes. Data types cannot be edited or deleted once they are associated with a unit (they become locked).
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/RPM/Help/Index/#_Toc434570749"/>
  </Information>

  <Information name="UnitManager">
    <description>
      With this interface you are able to manage (e.g. create, edit, delete) units which may be needed to define data attributes. Units cannot be edited or deleted once they are associated with a data attribute (they become locked).
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/RPM/Help/Index/#_Toc434570750"/>
  </Information>
</Informations>
