<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Informations>
  <Information name="Admin" fileName="SearchDesigner.cshtml">
    <description>
      With this interface you are able to customize the search component and define what fields of the
      metadata are searchable and how they appear in the application. Changes made through the interface will
      alter the Lucene configuration file on the server. For a detailed description of each parameter please
      refer to the Lucene User Manual provided with the installation package.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/ddm/Help/Index/#_Toc451435017" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="CreateDataset">
    <description>
      This wizard will assist you in creating a new dataset. Please select a data structure and a metadata structure below.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/ddm/Help/Index/#_Toc434570841" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="MetadataEditor">
    <description>
      <p>
        Here you can enter metadata for your new dataset. The form varies according to the metadata structure you selected in the first step.
        Mandatory fields are indicated with an red asterisk.
      </p>
      <p>You can add, remove, or re-order elements (e.g. multiple Creators) using the buttons at the right.</p>
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/ddm/Help/Index" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="structuredData">
    <description>
      <p>To download the entire dataset choose one of the following formats.</p>
      <p>Note: If you are the first one to download this dataset it may take a little longer, because the file has to be created.</p>
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/DCM/Help/Index/#_Toc451435014" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="ShowData">
    <description>
      This is a detailed Information on all parts of a dataset. Depending on your permissions your are able to Information, edit, or download either the metadata, the primary data or the data structure.<br />
      You may also set permissions for this particular dataset
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/ddm/Help/Index/#_Toc451435014" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="Help" fileName="Index.cshtml">
    <description>
      This guide will walk you through the basics of using search UI including how to manage search component.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="myDatasetGrid">
    <description>
      <p>This table contains all datasets, created by you as a current logged on user. </p>
      <p>By right clicking on the header, you can manage the visibility of columns. You can also use filtering or grouping to see the more operative informations.</p>
      <p>
        To Information more details of a dataset, click the <strong>Information details</strong> button available in each row.
      </p>
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="Home">
    <description>
      <p>
        Enter a phrase or keyword with at least 3 characters and press <b>Search</b>. You may select a category from the dropdown list in front of the searchfield to restrict your search (e.g Title).
      </p>
      <p>
        The search result contains all datasets where your term was found in the metadata.
        If configured by your system administrator the result list may
        also inlcude datasets where your search term was found in primary data
        (e.g. variable names, string values).
      </p>
      <p>To tweak the result list, click on the facets in the green area on the left or specify a filter in the header of the list. Clicking on a name in the column header will sort the results.</p>
      <p>To Information more details of a dataset, click the Information Details button available in each row.</p>
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/ddm/Help/Index" />
  </Information>
</Informations>