<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Information>
  <Information name="Error">
    <description>
      <p>In the case of any problems with authorization, please contact with your administrator.</p>
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="" />
  </Information>
  <Information name="Login">
    <description>
      <p>Through this interface you can login into the system.</p>
      <p>If you have not a username, you need to register into the system first.</p>
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/sam/help/index#_Login" />
  </Information>
  <Information name="MyAccount">
    <description>
      <p>This page summarizes your personal account information. Furthermore, you are able to edit that data, but there are two important facts you should be aware of:</p>
      <ol>
        <li>
          Password Change - You need to enter both, <i>Password</i> and <i>Confirm Password</i>.
        </li>
        <li>
          Security Question/Answer - You need to enter both, <i>Security Question</i> and <i>Security Answer</i>.
        </li>
      </ol>
      <p>Otherwise, the abovementioned properties aren't changed. </p>
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="DataPermissions">
    <description>
      Here you are able to manage how users (or groups) have access to individual datasets.
      Please select a dataset in the table below and specify who should have permissions to Information, update, delete, download data, or who is able to grant access to other users (Note: metadata is always free).
      Ticking the checkboxes "public access" in the upper table will make a dataset accessible without authentification (public access to primary data). Please use with care!
      By default only the creator of a dataset (in the system) has full access, all other permissions are not set, which means access is denied.
      Grants for individual users rule out higher level settings for groups.
      Please note that any change will take effect immediately without further confirmation or save/submit action.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/SAM/Help/Index/#_Toc451422050" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="Dataset">
    <description>
      With this interface you are able to see a list of Datasets. In this list you can see the status of each dataset and some useful actions for the maintenance of a dataset.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/SAM/Help/Index/#_Toc451422053" />
  </Information>
  <Information name="DatasetList">
    <description>
      This maintenance tool is meant for administrators only. All datasets are listed with their internal ID, status, and the option to remove them from the system. Use with care!
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/SAM/Help/Index/#_Toc451422053" />
  </Information>
  <Information name="DatasetPurge">
    <description>
      This maintenance tool is meant for administrators only. All datasets are listed with their internal ID, status, and the option to remove them from the system. Use with care!
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/SAM/Help/Index/#_Toc451422053" />
  </Information>
  <Information name="DatasetVersion">
    <description>
      This maintenance tool is meant for administrators only. All datasets are listed with their internal ID, status, and the option to remove them from the system. Use with care!
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/SAM/Help/Index/#_Toc451422053" />
  </Information>
  <Information name="DatasetVersions">
    <description>
      This maintenance tool is meant for administrators only. All datasets are listed with their internal ID, status, and the option to remove them from the system. Use with care!
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/SAM/Help/Index/#_Toc451422053" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="FeaturePermissions">
    <description>
      Here you are able to manage how users (or groups) have access to individual system features or entire modules.
      Please click on the name in the tree structure on left to Information individual permissions.
      Ticking the checkboxes in the navigation tree will make a feature accessible without authentification (public access).
      Please use with care!
      By default feature permissions are not set, which means access is denied unless access permissions are explicitly granted or inherited from an upper level feature (e.g. module).
      Individual grants on features rule out higher level settings. Effective permissions are shown in the first column of the table.
      Please note that any change will take effect immediately without further confirmation or save/submit action.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/SAM/Help/Index/#_Toc451422051" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="Groups">
    <description>
      With this interface you are able to manage groups. New groups can be added with the "Create" button. Existing groups can be edited (properties, members, delete) using the "Edit" button.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/SAM/Help/Index/#_Toc451422047" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="Help">
    <description>
      This guide will walk you through the basics of using administration parts including how to registrate or log on, how to manage users or groups and how to manage permissions.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="" />
  </Information>

  <Information name="Users">
    <description>
      With this interface you are able to manage users. New users can be added with the "Create" button. Existing users can be edited (properties, memberships, delete) through the "Edit" button.
    </description>
    <more text="More" title="go to help" path="/SAM/Help/Index/#_Toc451422044" />
  </Information>
</Information>